<resources>
    <string name="app_name">USTH Recipe App</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_explore">Explore</string>
    <string name="title_favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="background_image">background image</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign-in</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="re_enter_password">Re-enter password</string>
    <string name="already_have_an_account">Already have an account?</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="sign_in_as_guest">Sign-in as guest</string>

    <!-- Pasta -->
    <string name="pastaIngredients">- Pasta
        \n- Cream Cheese
        \n- Parmesan Cheese
        \n- Olive Oil
        \n- Garlic
        \n- Salt Pepper</string>
    <string name="pastaDesc">- Cook your pasta until it dense
        \n- Add cream cheese, pasta cooking water, parmesan, and stir well
        \n- Drain and add pasta to the skillet
        \n- Toss until well combined, adding some pasta water if needed</string>

    <!-- Maggi -->
    <string name="maggiIngredients">- Maggi Noodles
        \n- Water
        \n- Maggi Masala</string>
    <string name="maggieDesc">- Add one and half cup of water
        \n- Add maggi noodles and boil it
        \n- Add the maggi masala on to it
        \n- Wait for 2 minutes
        \n- Maggi is ready!</string>

    <!-- Cake -->
    <string name="cakeIngredients">- Cake
        \n- Water
        \n- 1 cup white sugar
        \n- 2 large eggs
        \n- 1/2 cup milk</string>
    <string name="cakeDesc">- Preheat the oven to 350 degrees F (175 degrees C).
        \n- Grease and flour a 9-inch square cake pan.
        \n- Cream sugar and butter together in a mixing bowl.
        \n- Combine flour and baking powder in a separate bowl.
        \n- Pour batter into the prepared cake pan.
        \n- Bake in the preheated oven until the top springs back when lightly touched, 30 to 40 minutes.
        \n- Remove from the oven and cool completely. Frost and enjoy!</string>

    <!-- Pancake -->
    <string name="pancakeIngredients">- Pancake
        \n- 1/2 cups all-purpose flour
        \n- 1/2 teaspoons baking powder
        \n- 1 tablespoon white sugar
        \n- 3 tablespoons butter, melted
        \n- egg</string>
    <string name="pancakeDesc">- Sift flour, baking powder, sugar, and salt together in a large bowl.
        \n- Heat a lightly oiled griddle or pan over medium-high heat.
        \n- Pour or scoop the batter onto the griddle, using approximately 1/4 cup for each pancake; cook until bubbles form and the edges are dry, about 2 to 3 minutes.
        \n- Flip and cook until browned on the other side.
        \n- Repeat with remaining batter.</string>

    <!-- Pizza -->
    <string name="pizzaIngredients">- Pizza
        \n- 1 1/2 cups (355 ml) warm water (105째F-115째F)
        \n- 1 package (2 1/4 teaspoons) active dry yeast
        \n- 3 3/4 cups (490g) bread flour
        \n- 2 tablespoons extra virgin olive oil (omit if cooking pizza in a wood-fired pizza oven)
        \n- 2 teaspoons kosher salt
        \n- 1 teaspoon sugar</string>
    <string name="pizzaDesc">- Add one and half cup of water
        \n- Preheat the pizza stone (or pizza pan or baking sheet): Place a pizza stone on a rack in the lower third of your oven. Preheat the oven to 475째F for at least 30 minutes, preferably an hour.
        \n- Divide the dough into 2 balls: Remove the plastic cover from the dough. Dust your hands with flour and push the dough down so it deflates a bit. Divide the dough in half.
        \n- Prep the toppings: Prepare your desired toppings. Note that you are not going to want to load up each pizza with a lot of toppings as the crust will end up not crisp that way.
        \n- Flatten the dough ball, and stretch out into a round: Working one ball of dough at a time, take one ball of dough and flatten it with your hands on a lightly floured work surface.
        \n- Brush the dough top with olive oil: Use your fingertips to press down and make dents along the surface of the dough to prevent bubbling.
        \n- Sprinkle the pizza peel with cornmeal, put flattened dough on top: Lightly sprinkle your pizza peel (or flat baking sheet) with cornmeal.
        \n- Bake: Bake pizza in the 475째F oven, one at a time, until the crust is browned and the cheese is golden, about 10 to 15 minutes.</string>

    <!-- Burgers -->
    <string name="burgerIngredients">- Burger
        \n- 1 pound (453 grams) 80% lean ground beef/chuck
        \n- 6 burger buns
        \n- 1 egg yolk
        \n- 1/2 small red or white onion
        \n- Ketchup
        \n- Handful fresh herbs, chopped roughly
        \n- 2 thinly sliced tomatoes
        \n- 6 slices of cheese
        \n- Lettuce leaves</string>
    <string name="burgerDesc">- Divide the ground beef. Divide the ground beef into 4 or 6 portions, depending on the number of burgers you would like to make.
        \n- Shape the patties. Gently press each portion of ground beef into a disk about 1-inch thick.
        \n- Warm the pan. Heat a pat of butter or a teaspoon of oil in a griddle or large skillet over medium heat.
        \n- Toast the buns. Working in batches if needed, place the bun halves cut-side down in the warm butter or oil. Toast until the surface is golden-brown.
        \n- Increase the heat to medium-high. Increase the heat to medium-high, and keep a careful eye on the pan.
        \n- Cook the burgers. Place the burger patties in the hot pan, leaving a little space between each one. Work in batches if necessary.
        \n- Flip the burgers. Quickly slide a spatula under the burgers and flip to the other side.
        \n- To make cheeseburgers. If making cheeseburgers, top the burgers with cheese as soon as you flip them.
        \n- Finish the burgers. When the burgers have finished cooking, transfer them to the toasted buns and finish with your favorite burger toppings.</string>

    <!-- Fries -->
    <string name="friesIngredients">- French Fries
        \n- 2 cups warm water
        \n- 1/3 cup white sugar
        \n- Large russet potatoes - peeled, and sliced into 1/4 inch strips
        \n- 6 cups vegetable oil for frying
        \n- Salt to taste</string>
    <string name="friesDesc">- Cut the potatoes
        \n- Soak the potatoes
        \n- Drain and dry the potatoes
        \n- Fry the potatoes
        \n- Drain and cool the half-done fries
        \n- Fry the potatoes again
        \n- Drain the fries
        \n- Serve your homemade French fries</string>

    <string name="load_more">Load More</string>
    <string name="title_activity_food_detail">Food Detail</string>

</resources>